

https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing/portfolio



Senior Digital Product Designer | UX/UI, Web, Html & CSS, Mobile, Motion Graphics, Social Videos

ABOUT ME

I'm about researching client and user/market needs and creating dynamic digital messaging and products by strategically using CTA's, typeface, colour and layouts/ wireframes that put user experience and user interface at the forefront.

UX/UI and **Product Design portfolio**

I'm a designer & I code HTML and CSS portfolio

Motion Graphics and Social Videos portfolio





Click to view

WORK EXPERIENCE

Borden Ladner Gervais LLP

Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia 🔇 Jan 2020 - Present 🖵 www.blg.com



- > Collaborate in the creation of company webpages for BLG.com and BLG Beyond; while applying best UX/UI practices, responsible for balancing speed, quality, and consistency of design with meeting firm objectives
- > Researching client and market needs and applying best site nav usage and webpage wireframes to determine optimized page patterns for best **UX/UI** results
- > Responsible for providing final web assets including hero banners; inline animated graphics and infographs; and adjusting page responsiveness for Desktop and Mobile experiences by injecting custom HTML and CSS code

Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP



- and working with wireframes; to providing final visual web assets including landing page banners, homepage animated banners, inline graphics and infographs, headshots, graphics for hover state flip tiles, and more
- > Working with HTML and CSS templates to facilitate client event eVites, working with CRM, B2B clients, spam filters and CASL compliance
- > Providing social media assets for LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram and Youtube; as well as assets for digital event signage, newsletters and internal communications as required

Thinkway Toys

Design Manager, Packaging and Productline Apr 2016 - Mar 2017



> Design Manager in licensed products and packaging creation: Lucas Films (Star Wars Rogue One), Disney/Pixar (Cars 3) and Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)

Consumer Product Designer Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

Canadian Tire, Toy R' Us, Dollarama, Uniqlo and more



Branded Consumer Products sold across Walmart Canada, Target Canada,

> Working with the team in leading 50+ licensees on 300+ products simultaneously and seasonally. Work days range from managing online product design approvals, to meeting with vendors communicating design goals and initiatives

<u>Dolce & Gabbana</u> (Milan, Italy)

Intern Sep 2012 - Oct 2013



> Having accumulated 10 years of fashion product development experience - I took my skills abroad and resulted in a work placement with Dolce & Gabbana at their head quarters in Milan for 10 months; duties include preparation of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections with direct exposure and experience to the European retail and client landscape

SKILLS





Figma































EDUCATION

Master Classes (IDF)

Storytelling Through Visual Design: with Ellen Lupton | Jan 2022

> Exploring visual design principles for desktop and mobile experiences through the exploration of storytelling and user journeys

General Assembly

Web Development Program Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

- > Web Dev Immersive Full Stack Program
- with UX/UI experience
- HTML5, CSS3, Sketch, Figma, JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, AJAX, SQL, SASS

Toronto Metropolitan University

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree Sep 1998 - Apr 2002

- Product Design, Graphic Design, Marketing, Trend Analysis
- Fashion Communication with focus in R&D, working in agile environments

Birmingham City University (UK)

Merchandising and Design Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

- > Selected by Ryerson University to partake in the London, UK exchange program
- Thesis: Triple P bottom line and relation to green design